Guide to the Lesly Lempert Collection, 1987-1994.
Lempert, Lesly Collection
- Series I. Periodicals
  - In the Public Interest: An Alternative Law Review, Spring, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    Producer: Center for Public Interest Law, State University of New York at Buffalo
  - A Call to Passover Peace Action (typescript, 5 leaves), [1989?] (Box 3, Folder 134)
    Producer: [Coalition of Jewish Organizations in North America]
  - Background on The Committee for Family Reunification, January 13, 1987; draft, typescript, 2 leaves (Box 3, Folder 135)
    Producer: Committee for Family Reunification
  - Committee to Protect Journalists: The First Ten Years, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    Producer: Committee to Protect Journalists
  - Excerpts from the CCINGO Seminar Held 14 June, 1991: Land Use Planning, June 14, 1991; transmission, 5 leaves (Box 3, Folder 137)
    Producer: Coordinating Committee of International NGOs (CCINGO)
  - Facts on the Ground: Settlement Policy, Human Rights and the New Rabin Government, October 20, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Paper on the Economic Effects of the Curfew to be Presented to European Community Policy-Makers, March 4, 1991; transmission, 8 leaves (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Press Briefing: The Pressures that NGOs are Facing During the Current Curfew, Febraury 21, 1991; transmission, 2 leaves (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Press Statement, February 28, 1991--February 21, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - (Press Statement): Update: The Effects of the Prolonged Curfew on the Palestinians in the Occupied Territories, February 28, 1991; transmission, 8 leaves (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - (Press Statement): Update: The Effects of the Curfew and the New Pass System on the Palestinians Living in the Occupied Territories, March 26, 1991; transmission, 5 leaves (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - (Press Statement): Undermining "Confidence Building Measures": Israel's Abuse of International Law in the West Bank and Gaza Strip, May 8, 1991; transmission, 7 leaves (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - (Press Statement): Update: The Crisis in the Occupied Territories: Unemployment, Poverty and Settlements, June 17, 1991; transmission, 3 leaves (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - (Press Statement): Six Months Later: The Noose Around the Occupied Territories Draws Tighter: The Effects of the War-Time Curfew, July 17, 1991; transmission, 9 leaves (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - (Press Statement): Update: Water Crisis in the Occupied Territories, February 28, 1992; transmission, 2 leaves (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Municipalities and Communities in Judea, Samaria & Gaza, June, 1990; transmission, 1 page (Box 3, Folder 142)
    Producer: Council of Jewish Communities in Judea Samaria & Gaza
  - Colonial Pursuits: Settler Violence During the Uprising in the Occupied Territories, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 143)
    Producer: DataBase Project on Palestinian Human Rights
  - Complaint Against Torture and Humiliation in Neve Tirza Prison, July 12, 1988; transmission, 2 leaves (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - From Palestinian Women Political Prisoners in Abu Kbir Prison, July 15, 1988; transmission, 2 leaves (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - Instutions Closed During the Uprising: January 1-September 30, 1989, October 1, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 146)
    Producer: DataBase Project on Palestinian Human Rights, Palestine Human Rights Information Center
  - Israeli Censorship in the Occupied Territories (Preliminary Report), [?] (Box 3, Folder 147)
    Producer: DataBase Project on Palestinian Human Rights, Palestine Human Rights Information Center, Karima Bennoune
  - Palestinian Women Political Prisoners in Israeli Prisons, August 12, 1988; transmission, 1 page (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - Report on Palestinian Women Prisoners, June 6, 1988; transmission, 4 leave (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - Uprising Update, March 1, 1989--July 1, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 150)
    Producer: Database Project on Palestinian Human Rights, Palestine Human Rights Information Center, Human Rights Research & Education Foundation
  - Uprising Update, September 1, 1989--November 1, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Country Reports on Human Rights Practices for 1989, February, 1990; photocopy, p. 1,400-1,591, 32 leaves (Box 3, Folder 152)
    Producer: Department of State
  - A Resource Guide: National News Media Outlets, January/February 1992; photocopy, p. 27 (Box 3, Folder 153)
    Producer: Fairness and Accuracy in Reporting (FAIR)
  - [Miscellaneous articles from Al-Fajr], January 16, 1989, 1990; photocopy, 2 leaves (Box 3, Folder 154)
    Producer: Al-Fajr
  - (Article): An Occupier's Way of Saying Happy New Year, January 16, 1989; photocopy (Box 3, Folder 154)
    Producer: Reem Nuseibeh, Al-Fajr
  - (Article): Seek End of Occupation, January 16, 1989; photocopy (Box 3, Folder 154)
    Producer: Judy Green, Gideon Freudenthal, Al-Fajr
  - Newsletter on Freedom of the Press, August 1990--June 1991 (Box 3, Folder 155)
    Producer: Forum of Action for Freedom of the Press and the Reopening of Derech haNitzotz/Tariq al Sharara
  - [Background Information] (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - Stuggle: A Newsletter on Israeli Democracy, March, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 156)
    Producer: Foundation for Democratic Education in Israel
  - Report on Israeli Settlement in the Occupied Territories, January 1991--November 1996 (Box 3, Folder 157)
    Producer: Foundation for Middle East Peace
    Volume/Number: 1.1, 1.3--3.2, 4.1--4.[2], 4.5--4.6, 5.[1], 5.3--5.4, 5.6, 6.2, 6.6
  - Review & Analysis: Arms Control & Proliferation in the Middle East, November, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 158)
  - Emergency Alert: Israeli Reservist Refuses to Serve in Gaza, September 3, 1993; transmission, 2 leaves (Box 3, Folder 159)
    Producer: Friends of Yesh Gvul
  - Newsletter, May, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 160)
  - The Undercover Units, October, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 160 A)
    Producer: Yesh Gvul
  - Israeli Censorship of Arab Publications, December, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 161)
    Producer: Fund for Free Expression, Meron Benvenisti
  - Agreement on the Gaza Strip and the Jericho Area, May 4, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 162)
    Producer: Government of Israel
  - The Seven Stars: A New Settlement Plan which Aims to Judaize the Arab Triangle and Eradicate the Green Line, February 12, 1992; book release, 2 versions (Box 3, Folder 163)
    Producer: Hanitzotz/A-Sharara Publishing House
  - (Attached article): Arabs decry Triangle housing for immigrants, [?]; photocopy (Box 3, Folder 163)
    Producer: Bill Hutman
  - (Attached article): Sharon's 'Seven Star' Plan: The 'Master Plan' to Judaize the Triangle, the Gallilee, and the Negev, August 5, 1991; photocopy (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - (Article): The Seven Stars Plan and Israeli Settlements in East Jerusalem: Text of Representation, May 17, 1992; typescript, 5 leaves (Box 3, Folder 163)
    Producer: Michal Schwartz
  - Sharon's Star Wars: Israel's Seven Star Settlement Plan, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 163)
    Producer: Michal Schwartz, Assaf Adiv, Hanitzotz A-Sharara Publishing House
  - [Typescripts of Haaretz Articles], June 13, 1991, June 21, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 164)
    Producer: Haaretz
  - (Article): The End of the Intifada (typescript, 5 leaves), June 13, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 164)
    Producer: Danny Rubenstein, Ha'aretz
  - (Article): Cruelly Murdered by Masked Men-Excerpts, June 21, 1991; typescript, 5 leaves (Box 3, Folder 164)
    Producer: Gideon Levy, Ha'aretz
  - [Collection of documents pertaining to Hanitzotz/Sharara], May 5, 1988--July 12, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 165)
    Producer: Hanitzotz/Sharara Organization, Derech Hanitzotz, Tariq A-Sharara
  - (Article): Lawyer says police seized clients' files, May 5, 1988; photocopy, 1 page (Box 3, Folder 165)
    Producer: Andy Court, Jerusalem Post
  - (Press Release): "We Will Torture Him Until You Talk", May 9, 1988; typescript, 2 leaves (Box 3, Folder 165)
    Producer: Hanitzotz/Sharara Organization
  - (Article): Hadas Lahav: The Shin Bet tried to make me "crazy", May 25, 1988; typescript, 2 leaves (Box 3, Folder 165)
    Producer: Lili Galili, Haaretz
  - (Affidavit): Affidavit of Roni Ben-Efrat, May 31, 1988; typescript, 1 page (Box 3, Folder 165)
    Producer: Roni Ben-Efrat
  - (Article): District judge allows bail to Derech Hanitzotz editors, June 14, 1988; photocopy (Box 3, Folder 165)
    Producer: Dvorah Getzler, Jerusalem Post
  - (Article): Barak reverses bail decision for Derech Hanitzotzeditors, June 17, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - (Article): The Four 'Derech Nitzotz' Detainees Protest Inhumane Conditions, June 29, 1988; typescript, 1 page (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - (Testimony): Attorney Netta Goldman After Visit to Mrs. Roni Ben-Efrat and Mrs. Michal Schwartz in Neveh Tirza, [June 29, 1988]; typescript, 1 page (Box 3, Folder 165)
    Producer: [Netta Ziv-Goldman] (attorney)
  - (Letter of transmittal): Solitary Appeal, July, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - [Letter of transmittal], July 6, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - (Letter of transmittal): Urgent Appeal, July 12, 1988; typescript, 1 page (Box 3, Folder 165)
    Producer: Fund for Freedom of Press
  - (Press Release): Declaration of the 4 Derech Hanitzotz Detainees in Neve Tirtza and Kishon Jails, July 27, 1988; transmission, 2 leaves (Box 3, Folder 165)
    Producer: Roni Ben-Efrat, Michal Schwartz
  - (Background Material): Derech Hanitzotz-Hebrew Weekly Suppressed, [?]; typescript, 2 leaves (Box 3, Folder 165)
    Producer: Derech Hanitzotz
  - [Call to Action of Police Minister Haim Bar Lev], [?]; typescript, 1 page (Box 3, Folder 165)
    Producer: [?]
  - (Public Appeal): Public Appeal by Yaacov Ben-Efrat and Assaf Adiv Regarding the Conditions of their Detention, [?]; typescript, 1 page (Box 3, Folder 165)
    Producer: Yacov Ben-Efrat, Assaf Adiv
  - (Document) Harrassment Campaign Against Hanitzotz/Sharara: Chronological Data, [?] (Box 3, Folder 165)
    Producer: [Hanitzotz/Sharara Organization]
  - Al-Haq Reiterates Call for an International Inquiry into the al-Harem al-Sharif Massacre, October 7, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 166)
    Producer: Al-Haq
  - Al-Haq's Response to the U.S. State Department Country Reports on Human Rights Practices for 1991: The Occupied Territories, May, 1991; photocopy, 21 leaves (Box 4, Folder 167)
  - “al-Haqq” tahuthth Majlis al-Amn al-Dawlī ‛alá al-radd bi-fā‛iliyah 'alá awāmir al-ib'ād ghayr al-qānūnīyah [Al-Haq urges the United Nations Security Council to React Effectively to the Illegal Deportation Orders] (Press release no. 56)., December 18, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 168)
  - Alert, September 23, 1989--October 15, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 169)
  - (Alert): Denial of Medical Care in Ansar III, September 23, 1989; transmission, 2 leaves (Box 4, Folder 169)
  - (Alert): Al-Haq Fieldworker Sha'wan Jabarin Hospitalized Following Beating in Detention, October 12, 1989; transmission, 2 leaves (Box 4, Folder 169)
  - (Alert): Al-Haq Fieldworker Sha'wan Jabarin Transferred to "The Cage" in Ansar 3, June 13, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 169)
  - (Alert): International Community Must Act to Halt Israel's Deportation of 12 Palestinians, January 7, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 169)
  - (Alert): Al-Haq Calls for the Provision of Adequate Medical Care for All Palestinian Detainees, September 11, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 169)
  - (Alert): Palestinian Community in Imminent Danger of More Deaths and Injuries as Prison Hunger Strike Continues, October 15, 1992; transmission, 1 page (Box 4, Folder 169)
  - An Ailing System: Israeli Military Government Health Insurance in the Occupied Palestinian Territories, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 170)
  - Ansar 3: A Case for Closure, August, 1988; photocopy (Box 4, Folder 171)
  - Appeal on Behalf of Al-Haq Fieldworkers, August 20, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 172)
  - The Applicability of Human Rights Law to Occupied Territories: The Case of the Occupied Palestinian Territories, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 173)
    Producer: Al-Haq, Linda Bevis
  - Application Denied: Separated Palestinian Families Tell Their Stories, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 174)
    Producer: Al-Haq, Rizeq Shuqair, Randa Siniora
  - Background Information on: Sha'wan Rateb 'Abdallah Al-Jabarin, [1989]; typescript, 3 pages (Box 4, Folder 175)
  - Briefing Papers on Twenty Years of Israeli Occupation of the West Bank and Gaza, [1987?] (Box 4, Folder 176)
  - Critique of the United States Department of State: Country Reports on Human Rights Practices for 1991: Israel and the Occupied Territories, March 11, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 177)
  - Dahriyyeh: Centre for Punishment, May, 1988; photocopy, 14 leaves (Box 4, Folder 178)
  - A Human Rights Assessment of the Declaration of Principles on Interim Self-Government Arrangements for Palestinians, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 179)
  - Human Rights Focus, April 4, 1991--June 1994 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - (Human Rights Focus): Restriction of Access to and Through East Jerusalem, April 4, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - (Human Rights Focus): The Illegal Use of Lethal Force Against "Fleeing Suspects", May 1, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - (Human Rights Focus): Israeli Land Acquisition in the Occupied Territories, August 20, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - (Human Rights Focus): Al-Haq's Interim Report on Mustafa 'Akkawi's Torture and Death: A Response to Israeli Police Investigation Results, February 14, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - (Human Rights Focus): Killings by Undercover and Uniformed Security Forces Increase; "Wanted" Palestinians Placed in Immediate Danger, May 12, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - (Human Rights Focus): Military Orders No. 1369 (West Bank) and No. 1076 (Gaza): A Grave Breach of IV Geneva Convention, August 25, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - (Human Rights Focus): Wilful Killings: A Sustained Israeli Policy in the Occupied Territories, November 21, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - (Human Rights Focus): Summary of an Ailing System: Israeli Military Government Health Insurance in the Occupied Palestinian Territories, July, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - (Human Rights Focus): Israel's First Report to the Committee Against Torture: Al-Haq's Response, June, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - The Human Rights of Persons with Disabilities, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 181)
  - Israel's War Against Education in the Occupied West Bank: A Penalty for the Future, November, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 182)
  - Jerusalem: Its Legal Status and the Possibility of a Durable Settlement, October, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 183)
  - Jnaid: The New Israel Prison in Nablus: An Appraisal, October, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 184)
    Producer: Al-Haq, Law in the Service of Man
  - Legal Consequences of the Demolition of Houses by Israel in the West Bank and Gaza Strip, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 185)
    Producer: Al-Haq, John Quigley
  - List of Publications, [1987?], 1993, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 186)
  - Newsletter, May/June 1986--April/June 1994 (Box 4, Folder 187)
    Volume/Number: 13--21, 23--27, 31--32
  - (Subject Index: Newsletters 9-21, October 1985-October 1987), October 1985-October 1987 (Box 4, Folder 187)
  - (Occaaional Paper No. 1): Administrative Detention in the Occupied West Bank, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    Producer: Al-Haq, Emma Playfair
  - (Occasional Paper No. 2): Israel's Deportation Policy in the Occupied West Bank and Gaza, August, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    Producer: Al-Haq, Joost Hiltermann
  - (Occasional Paper No. 4): Planning in Whose Interest? Land Use Planning as a Strategy for Judiazation, December, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    Producer: Al-Haq, Mona Rishmawi
  - (Occasional Paper No. 5): Demolition and Sealing of Houses as a Punitive Measure in the Israeli-Occupied West Bank, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 188)
  - (Occasional Paper No. 6): Perpetual Emergency: A Legal Analysis of Israel's Use of the British Defence (Emergency) Regulations, 1945, in the Occupied Territories, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    Producer: Al-Haq, Martha Roadstrum Moffett
  - (Occasional Paper No. 7): Enforcement of International Law in the Israeli-Occupied Territories, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    Producer: Al-Haq, Marc T.R. Stephens
  - (Occasional Paper No. 8): The Right to Unite: The Family Reunification Question in the Palestinian Occupied Territories: Law and Practice, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    Producer: Al-Haq, Candy Whittome
  - (Occasional Paper No. 9): An Illusion of Legality: A Legal Analysis of Israel's Mass Deportation of Palestinians on 17 December 1992), 1993 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    Producer: Al-Haq, Angela Gaff
    Volume/Number: 9
  - (Occasional Paper No. 10): Missiles and Dynamite: The Israeli Military Forces' Destruction of Palestinian Homes with Anti-Tank Missiles and High-Powered Explosives, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    Producer: Al-Haq, Tom Taylor
  - (Occasional Paper No. 12): The Right to Freedom of Assembly: An Analysis of the Position of the Palestinian National Authority, March, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    Producer: Al-Haq, Mustafa Mar'i
    Volume/Number: 12
  - Palestinian Victims of Torture Speak Out: Thirteen Accounts of Torture During Interrogation in Israeli Prisons, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 189)
  - Palestinians Wounded or Killed by IDF or Border Guard Bullets in the West Bank in 1986, October 20, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 190)
  - Tortur for Security: the systemic Torture and Ill-Treatment of Palestinians by Israel, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 190)
  - Press Briefing, October 13, 1987--May 11, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 191)
  - (Press Briefing): Army Brutality in the West Bank, October 13, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 191)
  - (Press Briefing): Shooting by the Israeli Armed Forces, October 19, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 191)
  - (Press Briefing): The Prisoners of the Uprising, May 11, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 191)
  - Press Release, February 15, 1987--April 21, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    Volume/Number: 7, 10--13, 15, 18, 47, 49, 56--57, 59--60
  - (Press Release): Continued Use of Gas Against Palestinian Political Prisoners, February 15, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 192)
  - (Press Release): An Appeal to State Signatories to the IV Geneva Convention to Intervene after Recent Killings, December, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 192)
  - (Press Release): A Further Appeal to States to Take Action to Stop Killings in the West Bank and Gaza, December 17, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 192)
  - (Press Release): Human Rights Violations Bound to Increase with Severance of Internation Communications, March 18, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 192)
  - (Press Release): Hundreds Detained in Desert Prison with Inadequate Water, April 2, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    Volume/Number: 13
  - (Press Release): Al-Haq Calls for the Immediate Closure of Ketziot/Ansar 3, May 31, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 192)
  - (Press Release): Al-Haq Calls for the Immediate Closure of Ansar 3 and Independent Investigation of Deaths at the Prison, August 17, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 192)
  - (Press Release): Al-Haq Issues an Interim Report on Mustafa 'Akkawi's Torture and Death: A Response to Israeli Police Investigation Results, February 14, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    Volume/Number: 47
  - (Press Release): Al-Haq's Documentation Reveals a Dramatic Increase in Killings of Palestinians in 1992, April 2, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    Volume/Number: 49
  - (Press Release): Al-Haq Urges the United Nations Security Council to Formulte an Effective Resposne to Israel's Illegal Deportations, December 18, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    Volume/Number: 56
  - (Press Release): Al-Haw Calls for the Prosecution of Perpetrators of Arbitrary or Summary Executions, February 12, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    Volume/Number: 57
  - (Press Release): Israeli Closure Divides Palestinian Community into Disconnected Regions, Isolates East Jerusalem, and Severly Disrupts Economic, Social, and Cultural Life, April 10, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    Volume/Number: 59
  - (Press Release): Al-Haq Urges States not to Abandon International Law, April 21, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    Volume/Number: 60
  - (Press Release): Third Urgent Appeal for Protective Measures for Palestinian Civilians Living Under Israeli Occupation, January 18 1991 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    Volume/Number: 40
  - Punishing a Nation: Human Rights Violations During the Palestinian Uprising December 1987-December 1988, December, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 193)
  - Press Release: Israel Moves to Evict 234 Palestinian Families, July 22, 1991; transmittal (Box 4, Folder 193 A)
    Producer: Gaza Center for Rights and Law
  - Urgent Request: The Administrative Detention of Dr. Rabah Hassan Abdul Aziz Mohana, Vice-President of the Arab Medical Association - Gaza, November 20, 1991; transmittal (Box 4, Folder 193 B)
  - Family Visits to Ansar III Begin Under Miserable Conditions After Three and a Half Years, October 28, 1991; photocopy of transmittal (Box 4, Folder 193 C)
  - Reconstruction of the Events of Late September 1996 in the West Bank and the Gaza Strip, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 194)
  - Reconstruction of Events (Revised): al-Haram al-Sharif, Jerusalem: Monday, 8 October 1990, October 28, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 195)
  - The Reply of the Law in the Service of Man/al-Haq to The U.S. Report on Human Rights Practices in the Territories Occupied by Israel for 1982 (second printing), January, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 196)
  - Stop Destorying Palestinian Homes, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 197)
  - (Stop Destorying Palestinian Homes): [Background], 1992 (Box 4, Folder 197)
  - (Stop Destorying Palestinian Homes): Al-Haq Survey 1 January 1981-31 December 1991, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 197)
  - (Stop Destorying Palestinian Homes): [Letter of Transmittal], 1992 (Box 4, Folder 197)
  - Stop Separating Palestinian Families, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 198)
  - (Stop Separating Palestinian Families): An International Campaign [background information], [?] (Box 4, Folder 198)
  - (Stop Separating Palestinian Families): Adopt-A-Family Scheme, April, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 198)
  - (Stop Separating Palestinian Families): List of Publications, [?] (Box 4, Folder 198)
  - (Stop Separating Palestinian Families): An International Campaign: Appeal, [?] (Box 4, Folder 198)
  - Summary of al-Haq's Taxation Report, [1989?] (Box 4, Folder 199)
  - Urban Planning in the West Bank Under Military Occupation: Summary Report, June, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 200)
  - Town Planning Under Military Construction: An Examination of the Law and Practice of Town Planning in the Occupied West Bank, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 200)
  - Excessive Secrecy, Lack of Guidelines: A Report on Military Censorship in the West Bank, November, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 200 A)
    Producer: Virgil Falloon, Al-Haq
  - Programme Report: 1986, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 200 B)
  - Justice?: The Military Court System in the Israeli-Occupied Territories, February, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 200 C)
    Producer: Paul Hunt, Al-Haq, Gaza Centre for Rights and Law
  - Taxation in the Occupied West Bank: 1967-1989, March, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 200 D)
    Producer: Marc Stephens, Al-Haq
  - Protection Denied: Continuing Israeli Human Rights Violations in the Occupied Palestinian Territories 1990, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 200 D)
  - Jerusalem Papers on Peace Problems, January 1974--June 1974 (Box 4, Folder 201)
    Producer: Hebrew University of Jerusalem
    Volume/Number: 1--3, 5, 7
  - (Jerusalem Papers on Peace Problems): Peace Conferences: The Formal Aspects, January, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 201)
    Producer: Hebrew University of Jerusalem, Raymond Cohen, Stuart Cohen
  - (Jerusalem Papers on Peace Problems): The Juridical Status of Jerusalem, February, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 201)
    Producer: Hebrew University of Jerusalem, Yehuda Zvi Blum
  - (Jerusalem Papers on Peace Problems): The Role of Great Power Guarantees in International Peace Agreements, February, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 201)
    Producer: Hebrew University of Jerusalem, Alan Dowty
  - (Jerusalem Papers on Peace Problems): Sharm al-Sheikh-Bab al-Mandeb: The Strategic Balance and Israel's Southern Approaches, March, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 201)
    Producer: Hebrew University of Jerusalem, Mordechai Abir
  - (Jerusalem Papers on Peace Problems): The Soviet Union and the Arab-Israel War of October 1973, June, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 201)
    Producer: Hebrew University of Jerusalem, Galia Golan